{
    "id": "d2dead173e1f4fe1a3f795be4450ed56",
    "title": "While, During, In, For | Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "81cb23e9a88044ef9caef05681721f50",
            "title": "During, While, In, For",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It rained …………… the night …………… an hour or two.",
                    "description": "We use during to say when something happens. We use for to say how long something lasts.",
                    "answers": [
                        "for, during",
                        "during, for",
                        "during, while",
                        "for, while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I met Julie ………………. my stay in America.",
                    "description": "We use during to say that something happens inside a particular period of time. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while",
                        "for",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was in Canada …………….. winter.",
                    "description": "We use during to say that something happens inside a particular period of time. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "for",
                        "during"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………… I was in Canada, I had some strange experiences.",
                    "description": "While is a conjunction. It is used to connect two clauses.",
                    "answers": [
                        "During",
                        "For",
                        "While"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was on holiday ……………….. June.",
                    "description": "Both during and in can be used to say that something happens inside a particular period of time.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "during",
                        "while",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will meet you …………….. lunchtime.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "John played tennis ………………. Alice went shopping.",
                    "description": "While is a conjunction. It is used to talk about two simultaneous actions or situations. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My family lived in Australia …………. five years.",
                    "description": "We use for to say how long something lasts.",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "for",
                        "in",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The shop was closed .......................... the whole of last month.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Peter was working in the garage .......................... Susie called.",
                    "description": "While is a conjunction. It is used to talk about two simultaneous actions or situations. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "while",
                        "during"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Yesterday we played tennis ....................... hours.",
                    "description": "We use for to say how long something lasts / lasted. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "for",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My parents visited us ........................... summer.",
                    "description": "We use during to say that something happens inside a particular period of time. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}